it is time to play chill dog or kill
dog dogs are supposedly man's best
friend but if Reddit has taught me
anything it's that that man is lying to
us man sure some pups have your back
when you need it but others will turn on
you faster than you can say attack pug
so remember this classic Vine right
here
[Applause]
a are you all right oh my God I'm okay
I'm okay thank you thank you it was just
a video
okay just a video not real so cute so
scary and such great comedic timing for
an animal that doesn't understand why
his balls have been taken away so so
comedians I'm going to show you a
picture of a pooch for 250 points I want
you to tell me if it's a chill dog or a
kill dog and then we'll reveal the
answer first one a radiant golden
retriever is he chill or kill Heather
and Campbell I'm going to say he's a
kill dog I don't know let's find out
look at him he's kill
dog
[Applause]
it K but he got super chill in the end
it was almost like he was almost like wh
I can't help it I'm sorry I'm really
sorry I get the he was walking right in
front of me next up this loyal lab chill
or kill
dog Heather and Campbell chill dog let's
find out please is it that same
dog I swear to dog I swear to I swear to
dog it's God backwards
this this dog is my spirit animal for
how I interact with the
internet come on guys stoping on
me all right now these unlikely best
friends you are a chill dog is that a
chill dog or a kill dog yes Noel
definitely a kill dog let's find out uh
oh don't be so short
oh but what I don't know what that is
that's like
a that's both yeah no that's it's not
very chill to teabag a cat so that is a
kill dog you were right it's freeing
he's trying to warm yeah I don't know if
that's what he's I don't know that's
what he's trying to do the cat looks
like a rug I mean yeah how was he
supposed to know I don't know but that
definitely that's chill flying dog I'm
interested to see how you chill in your
life sir
chill why are you putting your butt on
my face yo I'm
chill moving on this beautiful bear dog
does he chill or kill yes Derek this
dog's chill uh let's find
out oh help
him yeah
yay
because God forbid the head filming that
couldn't stop to help the cat yeah let's
make the dog do it
and finally we have a pair of pups will
we see a chill dog or a kill dog Derek
Waters I hate to say it there going to
be a kill dog all right let's find
out get him get
him go either way the correct answer was
both so you get points
okay